Welcome to the neighborhood...
Open House is a drama, horror, thriller film directed by Andrew Paquin.
A murderous couple invade a woman's home and hold her captive in the basement.
David, played by Brian Geraghty.
Alice, played by Rachel Blanchard.
Jennie, played by Anna Paquin.
Josh, played by Stephen Moyer.
Lila, played by Tricia Helfer.
Lauren, played by Jessica Collins.
Open House is a 2010 thriller film directed by Andrew Paquin.
Was screened at the 2010 Tribeca Film Festival.
It was released on DVD in August 2010 in the United States by Lionsgate.
The film features a cameo by the director's sister Anna
Paquin and her husband Stephen Moyer.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.